{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which anime heavily features music from the genre 'Eurobeat'?",
      "correct_answer": "Initial D",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Wangan Midnight", "Kino no Tabi", "Cowboy Bebop"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who was given the title 'Full Metal' in the anime series 'Full Metal Alchemist'?",
      "correct_answer": "Edward Elric",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Alphonse Elric", "Van Hohenheim", "Izumi Curtis"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the last name of Edward and Alphonse in the Fullmetal Alchemist series.",
      "correct_answer": "Elric",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Ellis", "Eliek", "Elwood"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In 'Inuyasha', what are the heros are looking to collect?",
      "correct_answer": "Jewel Shards",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Dragon Balls", "Rave Stones", "Sacred Stones"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the name of the corgi in Cowboy Bebop?",
      "correct_answer": "Einstein",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Edward", "Rocket", "Joel"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the name of the stuffed lion in Bleach?",
      "correct_answer": "Kon",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Jo", "Urdiu", "Chad"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In 'Fairy Tail', what is the nickname of Natsu Dragneel?",
      "correct_answer": "The Salamander",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Dragon Slayer", "The Dragon", "The Demon"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In the 9th Pokemon movie, who is the Prince of the Sea?",
      "correct_answer": "Manaphy",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Ash", "May", "Phantom"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the age of Ash Ketchum in Pokemon when he starts his journey?",
      "correct_answer": "10",
      "incorrect_answers": ["11", "12", "9"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is the true moon princess in Sailor Moon?",
      "correct_answer": "Sailor Moon",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Sailor Venus", "Sailor Mars", "Sailor Jupiter"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What was Ash Ketchum's second Pokemon?",
      "correct_answer": "Caterpie",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Charmander", "Pikachu", "Pidgey"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is the main character with yellow hair in the anime Naruto?",
      "correct_answer": "Naruto",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Ten Ten", "Sasuke", "Kakashi"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The name of Junko Enoshima's imposter at the beginning of Danganronpa: Trigger Happy Havoc is?",
      "correct_answer": "Mukuro Ikusaba",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ryota Mitarai",
        "Ultimate Imposter",
        "Komaru Naegi"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In 'Future Diary', what is the name of Yuno Gasai's Phone Diary?",
      "correct_answer": "Yukiteru Diary",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Murder Diary", "Escape Diary ", "Justice Diary "]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In the anime Noragami who is one of the main protagonists?",
      "correct_answer": "Yukine",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Karuha", "Mineha", "Mayu"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In the anime Seven Deadly Sins what is the name of one of the sins?",
      "correct_answer": "Diane",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Sakura", "Ayano", "Sheska"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In the anime Black Butler, who is betrothed to be married to Ciel Phantomhive?",
      "correct_answer": "Elizabeth Midford",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Rachel Phantomhive",
        "Alexis Leon Midford",
        "Angelina Dalles"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In 'The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya' series, the SOS Brigade club leader is unknowingly treated as a(n) __ by her peers.",
      "correct_answer": "God",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Alien", "Time Traveler", "Esper"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In 'A Certain Scientific Railgun', how many 'sisters' did Accelerator have to kill to achieve the rumored level 6?",
      "correct_answer": "20,000",
      "incorrect_answers": ["128", "10,000", "5,000"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What caused the titular mascot of Yo-Kai Watch, Jibanyan, to become a yokai?",
      "correct_answer": "Being run over by a truck",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ate one too many chocobars",
        "Through a magical ritual",
        "When he put on the harmaki"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is the author of the manga series 'Astro Boy'?",
      "correct_answer": "Osamu Tezuka",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Mitsuteri Yokoyama",
        "Takao Saito",
        "Yoshihiro Tatsumi"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "On what medium was 'Clannad' first created?",
      "correct_answer": "Visual novel",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Anime", "Manga", "Light novel"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In Digimon, what is the Japanese name for the final evolutionary stage?",
      "correct_answer": "Ultimate",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Mega", "Adult", "Champion"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In the 2012 animated film 'Wolf Children', what are the names of the wolf children?",
      "correct_answer": "Ame & Yuki",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Hana & Yuki", "Ame & Hana", "Chuck & Anna"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The characters of 'Log Horizon' are trapped in what game?",
      "correct_answer": "Elder Tale",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Sword Art Online", "Tower Unite", "Yggdrasil"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The two main characters of 'No Game No Life', Sora and Shiro, together go by what name?",
      "correct_answer": "Blank",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Immanity", "Disboard", "Warbeasts"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Satella in 'Re:Zero' is the witch of what?",
      "correct_answer": "Envy",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Pride", "Sloth", "Wrath"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which of the following originated as a manga?",
      "correct_answer": "Akira",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Cowboy Bebop", "High School DxD", "Gurren Lagann"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What year did 'Attack on Titan' first air?",
      "correct_answer": "2013",
      "incorrect_answers": ["2014", "2012", "2015"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In 'To Love-Ru', Ren and Run are from what planet?",
      "correct_answer": "Memorze",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Deviluke", "Mistletoe", "Okiwana"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is the colossal titan in 'Attack On Titan'?",
      "correct_answer": "Bertolt Hoover",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Reiner", "Eren", "Sasha"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is the armored titan in 'Attack On Titan'?",
      "correct_answer": "Reiner Braun",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Armin Arlelt", "Mikasa Ackermann", "Eren Jaeger"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In Ms. Kobayashi's Dragon Maid, who is Kobayashi's maid?",
      "correct_answer": "Tohru",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Lucoa", "Kanna", "Elma"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In 2013, virtual pop-star Hatsune Miku had a sponsorship with which pizza chain?",
      "correct_answer": "Domino's",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Papa John's", "Pizza Hut", "Sabarro's"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "How many 'JoJos' that are protagonists are there in the series 'Jojo's Bizarre Adventure'?",
      "correct_answer": "8",
      "incorrect_answers": ["6", "4", "5"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What animation studio produced 'Gurren Lagann'?",
      "correct_answer": "Gainax",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Kyoto Animation", "Pierrot", "A-1 Pictures"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the theme song of 'Neon Genesis Evangelion'?",
      "correct_answer": "A Cruel Angel's Thesis",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Stardust Crusaders",
        "Requiem for a Dream",
        "God Knows"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the name of Funny Valentine's stand in Jojo's Bizarre Adventure Part 7, Steel Ball Run?",
      "correct_answer": "Dirty Deeds Done Dirt Cheap",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Filthy Acts Done For A Reasonable Price",
        "Civil War",
        "God Bless The USA"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which Pokémon and it's evolutions were banned from appearing in a main role after the Episode 38 Incident?",
      "correct_answer": "The Porygon Line",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The Pikachu Line",
        "The Elekid Line",
        "The Magby Line"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is the main heroine of the anime, Full Metal Panic!",
      "correct_answer": "Kaname Chidori",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Teletha Testarossa", "Melissa Mao", "Kyoko Tokiwa"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which part from the JoJo's Bizarre Adventure manga is about a horse race across America?",
      "correct_answer": "Part 7: Steel Ball Run",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Part 6: Stone Ocean",
        "Part 3: Stardust Crusaders",
        "Part 5: Golden Wind"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What name is the main character Chihiro given in the 2001 movie 'Spirited Away'?",
      "correct_answer": "Sen (Thousand)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Hyaku (Hundred)",
        "Ichiman (Ten thousand)",
        "Juu (Ten)"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the name of JoJo's Bizarre Adventure Part 5?",
      "correct_answer": "Vento Aureo",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Vento Oreo", "Vanto Aureo", "Vento Eureo"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In the Naruto manga, what is the last name of Tsunade?",
      "correct_answer": "Senju",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Haruno", "Uzumaki", "Yamanaka"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In the anime 'My Hero Academia', which character is shown with the ability to manipulate gravity?",
      "correct_answer": "Uraraka",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Bakugo", "Deku", "Asui "]
    }
  ]
}
